Fowler C. West papers, Inclusive: 1964-2009, Bulk: 1965-1993
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), 1975-1993; 2
  - Advisory Committee on CFTC-State Cooperation, 1983-1992; 2
    - Commodity Pools, 1983-1991; 3
      - Regulate Off-Exchange Commodity Investments, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Model State Commodity Code, 1984-1986; 4
      - Correspondence, 1985 October-November (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Press Releases, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Testimony, Fowler West before Senate Financial Institutions Committee, 1986 February 4 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Tracking Violators, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Speeches, 1983-1986; 5
      - Brookings Institute 1983 Economics for Journalists Program, 1983 September 22 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Operations Division of Future Industry Association, 1983 November 22 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - CFTC Enforcement Seminar, 1983 October 20 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - CFTC Regional Seminar on Cooperative and State Enforcement Actions, 1984 February 1 (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - Futures Industry Association Law and Compliance Division, 1984 February 16 (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - Futures Committee of the Federal Bar Association, 1984 April 24 (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - Briefing on New Program to Combat Fraud in the Commodities Industry by the National Futures Association and CFTC, 1984 May 29 (Box 7, Folder 26)
      - CFTC Enforcement Seminar, 1986 February 19 (Box 7, Folder 27)
      - National Futures Association (draft), 1986 February 20 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Campaign I, 1975-1982; 3
    Campaigns I and II subseries’ document West’s appointment to the CFTC in 1982 and 1988, and include the nomination and confirmation process in the U.S. Senate. Present are “Alpha Files,” hundreds of letters to and from members of Congress that West maintained during the process. Correspondence between the White House and West are also included.
    - General, 1975-1982; 1
      - Appointment Documents, 1982 September 17 (Box 7, Folder 29)
      - Biography, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 30)
      - Background Paper, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 31)
      - Hearing, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 32)
      - History of Office Terms, 1975-1982 (Box 7, Folder 33)
      - Oath of Office, 1982 October 6 (Box 7, Folder 34)
      - Paper- “Legislative History of the CFTC”, 1982 February (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Personal Notes, 1981 December 9-1982 February 24 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Personal Notes, 1982 February 24-March 23 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Personal Notes, 1982 March 23- April 14 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Personal Notes, 1982 April 14-May 14 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Personal Notes, 1982 May 14- September 1 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Personal Notes, 1982 September 2-October 6 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Press Articles, 1982 March-June (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Photograph, Fowler C. West, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Senate Confirmation, 1981-1982; 2
      - Agenda, 1982 September 29 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Committee Print, 1982 September 29 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Committee Questions, 1982 September 29 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Congressional Record-Daily Digest, 1982 September 28-30 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - Courtesy Call Notes, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Executive Calendar, 1982 October 1 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Financial Disclosure, 1982 June (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Financial Disclosure, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Photographs, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - Recommendation Letters to Reagan, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 19)
      - Research, Philip Johnson Confirmation Hearing, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - Statements, Hon. Roger Jepsen, 1982 September 29 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Statements, Hon. Thomas S. Foley, 1982 September 29 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Statements, Hon. Marvin Leath, 1982 September 29 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Statements, Fowler C. West, 1982 September 29 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Support, Alpha Files, “A-F”, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Support, Alpha Files, “G-K”, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Support, Alpha Files, “L-O”, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Support, Alpha Files, “P-Z”, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Support, Alpha Files, “Boll Weevil,” First Letter, 1982 February 16 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Support, Alpha Files, “Boll Weevil,” Second Letter, 1982 March 31 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Support, Alpha Files, “Boll Weevil,” Third Letter, 1982 June 5 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Support, Alpha Files, “Boll Weevil,” Fourth Letter, 1982 December 6 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Support, Hon. Marvin Leath, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Testimony Advice, 1982 June (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Campaign II, 1987-1988; 4
    - Appointment Affidavits, 1988 August 2 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Congratulations, 1988 April-May (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Congressional Record, Vol. 134, No. 84, 1988 June 9 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Hearing, Reappointment of Fowler C. West and Nomination of William W. Erwin, Before the Committee on Agriculture, Nutrition, and Forestry, United States Senate, 1988 June 7 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - News Clippings, 1987 June-1988 April (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Reappointment Evaluation, 1988 May (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Support, Alpha Files, “A-J”, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Support, Alpha Files, “K-P”, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Support, Alpha Files, “R-Z”, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - “Weekly Compilation of Presidential Documents,” Vol, 24, No. 16, Page 501, 1988 April (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - White House Press Release, 1988 April 20 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1982-1992; 5
    The Correspondence subseries is arranged chronologically.
    - General, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - General (1 of 3), 1983 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - General (2 of 3), 1983 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - General (3 of 3), 1983 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - General (1 of 3), 1984 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - General (2 of 3), 1984 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - General (3 of 3), 1984 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - General (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - General (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - General (1 of 3), 1986 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - General (2 of 3), 1986 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - General (3 of 3), 1986 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - General (1 of 3), 1987 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - General (2 of 3), 1987 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - General (3 of 3), 1987 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - General (1 of 3), 1988 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - General (2 of 3), 1988 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - General (3 of 3), 1988 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - General (1 of 3), 1989 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - General (2 of 3), 1989 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - General (3 of 3), 1989 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - General (1 of 3), 1990 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - General (2 of 3), 1990 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - General (3 of 3), 1990 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - General, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - General, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Dissents and Separate Views, 1986-1993; 6
    Dissents and Separate Views are arranged alphabetically by case name and show the issues that were adjudicated to the level of the full Commission. An item level inventory of the binders is provided as a PDF.
    - Cases, “A-F”, 1986-1993 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Cases, “G-K”, 1988-1992 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Cases, “L-R”, 1987-1992 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Cases, “S-Z’, 1986-1992 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Meetings, 1980-1993; 7
    The Meetings subseries has been arranged in original order as much as possible, thus papers are mostly chronological. Generally, these files contain memos concerning business discussed at each commission meeting, such as applications for designation as contract market in various option areas. There are also notebooks for each quarter reporting on the staff, programs, statistics, and objectives of the CFTC. Memos from the CFTC’s Division of Enforcement, Division of Trading and Markets, and Division of Economic Analysis are represented throughout the meeting files. A variety of futures markets are represented in the committee files. Documents dealing with major exchanges and boards of trade are also found in this series.
    - Agriculture Advisory Committee, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Kansas City Board of Trade/Value Line Composite Average, 1980 February 16 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - PSI, 1982 January 26 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange Contract Market, 1984 January 11 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange Mutual Offset System and Singapore, 1984 August 28 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - National Futures Association Briefing, 1985 April 30 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Amendments to Contract Market Designations, 1985 August 13 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - New York Futures Exchange Contract Market, 1986 May 20 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Chicago Board of Trade Petition, 1987 September 8 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange Treasury Index, 1988 February 25 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Program Objectives 3rd Quarter FY88, 1988 February 25 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Chicago Board of Trade Contract Market Mortgage Backed Futures, 1988 April 19 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Chicago Board of Trade Contract Market Silver Futures, 1988 April 19 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - MidAmerica Commodity Exchange, 1988 April 19 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Chicago Board of Trade/Board of Exchange, 1988 May 11 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Chicago Board of Trade Contract Market Medium Term, 1988 May 11 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Program Objectives 4th Quarter FY88, 1988 May 26 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange Contract Futures Silver Market, 1988 June 25 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Chicago Board of Trade Contract Market 30-Day Interest Rate Futures, 1988 July 26 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - American Futures Corporation Enforcement, 1988 July 26 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Enforcement John N. Kyle, II, 1988 July 26 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Program Objectives, First Quarter FY89, 1988 September 13 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Program Objectives, Second Quarter FY89, 1988 December 13 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Hybrid Instruments Rules, 1989 March 27 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Enforcement Activity, Second Quarter FY89, 1989 May 23 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Enforcement, CFTC and Colorado v. Morrison, 1989 May 23 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Enforcement, Rand -Bond of North America, 1989 May 23 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Enforcement, Rochschild International, et al., 1989 May 23 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Program Objectives Fourth Quarter FY89, 1989 June 1 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange Sale Practice Audit Program, 1989 June 20 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Enforcement, Thomas J. Johnson, 1989 June 20 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Enforcement, Paul Sarnoff, Herbert Culpepper, 1989 June 20 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Enforcement, Stanford Management Corporation, 1989 June 20 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Enforcement, Elliot Thaler, Richard S. Rogers, 1989 June 20 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Enforcement, Woodstock Trading Company, 1989 June 20 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Enforcement, Steven C. Brenner, 1989 June 20 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange Contract Market British Pound Sterling, 1989 June 29 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange Contract Market, Pound Sterling, Japanese Yen, West German Deutsche Mark, 1989 June 29 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Agenda, Commission Meeting, 1989 August 29 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Enforcement, McFarlin Trading Company, 1989 December 9 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Self-Regulatory Organization Committees and Disciplinary Histories, 1990 February 27 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - New York Mercantile Exchange Contract Market Natural Gas Futures, 1990 February 27 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Program Objectives Fourth Quarter FY90, 1990 June 6 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Chicago Board of Trade and Tokyo Stock Price Index, Japanese Govt. Bonds, 1990 June 20 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Chicago Board of Trade Contract Market, Three Month European Currency Unit Interest Rate Futures, 1990 November 27 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Program Objectives Second Quarter FY91, 1990 December 4 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Chicago Board of Trade Contract Market, Cash Settled Three Year/5 Year Interest Rate Swap Futures, 1991 January 29 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange Contract Market Broiler Chickens Futures, 1991 January 29 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - MidAmerica Commodity Exchanges Contract Market Corn Futures, 1991 January 29 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Chicago Board of Trade Contract Market, Cash Settled Three Year/5 Year Interest Rate Swap Futures, 1991 February 26 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Chicago Board of Trade Contract Market Short Term US Treasury Futures, 1991 February 26 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Commodity Exchange Inc. Contract Market Gold Asset Participation Futures, 1991 February 26 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - MidAmerica Commodity Exchange Contract Market US Treasury Bond Futures, 1991 February 26 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Program Objectives Third Quarter FY91, 1991 February 26 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Twin Cities Board of Trade Contract Market British Pound, Deutsche Mark Cross Currency Futures Contract, 1991 February 26 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Chicago Board of Trade Contract Market Three Month European Currency Unit Interest Rate Futures, 1991 March 25 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Coffee, Sugar and Cocoa Exchange Contract Market Euro-Differential Coffee Futures, 1991 March 25 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Commodity Exchange, Inc. Contract Market Five Day Physical Gold Option Contracts, 1991 March 25 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Chicago Board of Trade Contract Market Long Term French Government Bond Futures, 1991 April 30 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange Contract Market Six Currency Cross-Rate Futures, 1991 April 30 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange Contract Market One Month LIBOR Futures, 1991 April 30 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Program Objectives, Fourth Quarter FY91, 1991 May 21 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Chicago Board of Trade for Contract Market Diammonium Phosphate Futures, 1991 July 25 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Chicago Board of Trade for Contract Market German Government Bond Futures Contracts, 1991 July 25 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Registration Rules, 1991 July 25 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Enforcement, CFTC v. Sun Hing Bullion Investment, 1991 December 9 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Enforcement, Noble Metals Int., Moorgate Ltd., 1991 December 9 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Enforcement, Donald P. Damaso, 1991 December 17 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Enforcement, Bruce Alan Drezner, 1991 December 17 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Federal Register Revision of Contract Market Designation, 1992 January 22 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Financial Products Advisory Committee, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - CPO and CTA Requirements, 1992 January 22 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - MidAmerica Commodity Exchange Contract Market Rough Rice Futures, 1992 January 22 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Accredited Investor Concept in Exemptions from State Securities Registration Requirements, 1992 January 22 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Quarterly Review First Quarter, FY92, 1992 January 22 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange Contract Market Poor’s Midcap 400 Stock Price Index Futures, 1992 February 11 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - New York Mercantile Exchange Contract market in Gulf Coast Unleaded Regular Gasoline, 1992 February 11 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - New York Mercantile Exchange Contract Market Natural Gas Futures, 1992 March 3 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Chicago Board of Trade for Contract Market in Health Insurance Futures, 1992 March 31 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Coffee, Sugar & Cocoa Exchange Contract Market Brazil Differential Coffee Futures, 1992 March 31 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Quarterly Review Second Quarter FY92, 1992 April 21 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Chicago Board of Trade Contract Market in Ferrous Scrap Futures, 1992 May 26 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Regulation Rules, 1992 May 26 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Chicago Board of Trade for designation as a Contract Market Canadian Government Bond Futures, 1992 July 30 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - MidAmerica Commodity Exchange Contract Market Three-Month Euro-Dollar Time Deposit futures, 1992 July 30 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Quarterly Review, Third Quarter FY92, 1992 July 30 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Relief Requirements for CPOs and CTAs, 1992 July 30 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Chicago Board of Trade Contract Market in CBOT International Commodity Index futures, 1992 July 30 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Commodity Exchange Contract Market Platinum and Palladium Futures, 1992 August 11 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Chicago Board of Trade for Contract Market Clean Air Futures, Barge Freight Rate Index for grain shipments, Agricultural Index futures, 1992 September 25 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Chicago Board of Trade’s Proposed Project Trading System, 1992 October 19 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - MidAmerica Commodity Exchange Contract Market in MidAm U.S. Dollar Composite Index futures, 1992 October 19 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Recordkeeping Requirements, 1992 October 19 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Proposed Rule Revisions Hybrid Instruments, 1992 November 5 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - MidAmerica Commodity Exchange Contract Market Medium-Term U.S. Treasury Note Futures, Three-month Eurodollar Time Deposit Futures, U.S. Dollar composite Index Futures, 1992 November 5 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Quarterly Review Fourth Quarter FY92, 1992 November 5 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Proposed Rules Exempting SWAP Agreements, 1992 November 5 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Broker Association Registration, 1992 November 24 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Swaps and Hybrids, Final Rules, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Swaps and Hybrids, Proceedings, 1993 January 14 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Swaps and Hybrids, Statement Fowler C. West, 1993 January 14 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - News Clippings, 1982-1993; 8
    News Clippings are arranged chronologically, documenting national press coverage of West and the CFTC.
    - General, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - General, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - General, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - General, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - General, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - General, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - General, 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - General, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - General, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - General, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Memos, and Notes, 1977-1991; 9
    The Publications, Memos, and Notes subseries is arranged by format.
    - Articles, 1977-1981 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Articles by West, 1983-1991 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Book Review: Securities Arbitration by Fowler C. West, 1989 May (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Book Review: Securities Arbitration, 1989 May (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Memos, CFTC-SEC Cooperation, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Memos, Insider Trading and Futures Markets, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Memos, Anticipated Budget Needs, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Notes, Fraud, circa 1985 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Paper, “Customer Protection...”, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Paper, “Commodity Fraud and the Elderly,”, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Paper, “Combating Commodity Fraud”, 1984 May (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Paper, “Commodity Fraud and the Elderly”, 1987 December (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Paper, “History of Arbitration in the Futures Industry and Its Interaction with the Commission’s Reparation Program”, 1987 September (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Speeches and Statements, 1983-1993; 10
    Speeches and Statements subseries is arranged chronologically.
    - CFTC-SEC Policy on Non-Diversified Stock Indices, 1984 January 18 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - National Futures Industry Conference, 1983 March 4 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Trade Abuses, 1983 March 29 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Committee on Futures Regulation of the Federal Bar Association, 1983 April 11 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Before the Directors of the National Grain Trade Council, 1983 May 17 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Before the Commodity Club of Washington [Not Delivered], 1983 June 13 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Agricultural Options Advisory Committee Organizational Meeting, 1983 June 23 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Valdosta Lion’s Club, 1983 August 30 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Brookings Institution 1983 Economics for Journalists Program, 1983 September 22 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Kent Law School Conference, 1983 September 29 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - The Futures Markets and National Policy, An Agenda for the 1980’s, 1983 October 6 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Commodity Futures Trading Commission Division of Enforcement Seminar, 1983 October 20 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Before the Commodity Club of Washington, D.C., 1983 November 9 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Operations Division of the Futures Industry Association, Inc., 1983 November 22 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Chicago Bar Association Commodity Law Committee and Futures Industry Association Law and Compliance Division, 1983 December 16 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Joint Economic Committee, 1984 January 23 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Before the Commodity Futures Trading Commission Regional Seminar on Cooperative and State Enforcement Actions, 1984 February 1 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - American Society of Public Administrators, 1984 February 8 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Before the Futures Industry Association Law and Compliance Division, 1984 February 16 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Mid America Commodity Exchange Opening, 1984 February 21 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Futures Industry Association, 1984 March 5 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Futures Committee of the Federal Bar Association, 1984 April 24 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Advisory Committee on CFTC-State Cooperation, 1984 May 8 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - New Program to Combat Consumer Fraud in the Commodities Industry by the National Futures Association in Cooperation with the CFTC, 1984 May 29 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Statement, 1984 June 12 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Educational Seminar on Agricultural Commodity Options for the Southwestern Cotton Industry, 1984 September 7 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Seventh Annual Commodities Law Institute Panel on CTA/CPO Issues, 1984 September 21 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Adding Audit Trail Issue to Quarterly Objective, 1984 October 10 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Third Annual Seminar on State Cooperative Enforcement Actions, 1984 October 18 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Panel Discussion at CFTC-Jurisdictional Issues, 1984 October 23 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Statement, Commission Meeting, 1984 Dec 20 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Commission Approval of Rule 1.55 (d), 1985 Feb 5 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - 10th Annual National Futures Industry Conference, 1985 March 8 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Chicago-Kent College of Law Eight Annual Commodities Law Institute Panel on FCM Issues, 1985 October 3 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Statement, Mark Young, circa 1985 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Audit Trail Final Rules, 1986 January 14 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Senate Financial Institutions Committee, The Honorable Ray Moore, Chairman, 1986 February 04 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Address Before the CFTC Enforcement Seminar, 1986 February 19 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Futures Industry Association Annual Conference, 1986 March 7 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Considering the New York Futures Exchange’s Proposal, 1986 May 20 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Concept Release: Hybrid Debt-Option Instruments, 1986 August 27 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - FCW Speech Outline, Enforcement Seminar, 1986 November 14 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Before the Banking, Commerce, and Insurance Committee Nebraska State Legislature, 1987 February 20 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - In Support of Bill LB575 Before the Senate Banking, Commerce, and Insurance Committee Nebraska State Legislature, 1987 February 23 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - In Support of A.B. 203 Before the Nevada Assembly Commerce Committee, 1987 March 9 (Box 27, Folder 25)